Contact

laveshbhama90@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lavesh-bhama-161a8720 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Extract, Transform, Load (ETL)

Data Visualization

Certifications
Oracle SQL Expert

Lavesh Bhama

Information Technology Officer at CENTRAL BANK OF INDIA Indore

Summary

IT professional with a demonstrated history of working in both the Indian private sector as well as public.

Vast skillset under the business intelligence umbrella. Not limited to data wareshouse developer with Informatica, Talend alongside Tableau, BO as BI developer.

Accompanied by experience with OLAP (Datawareshouse & Data Lake) and OLTP systems, exposing various database platforms viz., Teradata, Oracle, Greenplum.

Buckled up for Python.

Experience

CENTRAL BANK OF INDIA

Information Technology Officer
May 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra

Catering to the critical data needs across departments within the bank besides deliverables to statutory bodies, regulators and Indian government.

Tata Consultancy Services

4 years 5 months

System Engineer

January 2013 - May 2017 (4 years 5 months)

Business Intelligence Developer.

System Engineer

2013 - May 2017 (4 years)

Business Intelligence Developer

Education

Acopolis

Bachelor's Degree, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2008 - 2012)

Kendriya Vidyalaya

· (2007 - 2011)